One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Inherited will...
Miras alınan irade,
the tides of time, and humanity's dreams...
zamanın gelgitleri ve insanların hayalleri...
They cannot be stopped.
Bunların önüne geçilemez.
As long as people seek freedom,
Özgürlüğe aç olan insanlar oldukça...
these things will never cease to be.
bunlar hep var olacak.
I only believe in the future -- I don't care if anyone laughs
Sadece geleceğe inanırım, gülen gülsün, aldırmam pek
That racing passion makes you shine
Bu yarış tutkusu seni öne çıkarır hep
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
Çok parlak ama yine de bakmak istiyorum
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
Bir yerlerde "estetiği" hissediyorum
I follow, follow in the footsteps
İzindeyim, hiçbir şeye benzemeyen
of a dream that resembles no one
bir hayalin izindeyim, yeniden
Until I dramatically get it
Ta ki dramatik bir anla ulaşana dek,
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
Görülmeyen bu hayalin peşine düşeceğim,
of a dream no one can see
onu yakalayıp gerçeğe dönüştüreceğim.
I'm going to go with you, so passionate feelings
Seninle gideceğim, bu tutkuyla yanacağım
I don't really need everything to add up
Her şeyin mantıklı olmasına gerek yok zaten
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
Sıradan bir hayatı bırakıp
run for paradise instead
CENNETE koş hemen,
Reverse Mountain
Reverse Mountain
What's wrong, Zoro?
Sorun ne, Zoro?
You've had a serious look on your face for a while.
Yüzün bir an ciddi bir ifadeye büründü.
Well, I might just be imagining things, but...
Umarım sadece hayal gücümdür.
But what?
O ne?
I feel like the ship hasn't moved in a while.
Sanırım bu gemi, bir süredir hareket etmiyor.
What?
Ne?
Now that you mention it, the sail isn't catching any wind...
Düşününce, yelken hiç rüzgâr almıyor...
Oh no...!
Olamaz...!
We've entered the Calm Belt!
Calm Belt'e girdik!
The Balm Belt?
Charm Belt mi?
The heck is that?
O ne lan?
The Calm Belt! A sea where nothing moves a muscle!
Calm Belt! Hiçbir şeyin kıpırdamadığı bir deniz!
You grew some muscle?
Bu senin gücün mü?
No, you idiot!
Seni salak!
Was that an earthquake?
Deprem miydi o?
An earthquake? But we're at sea.
Deprem mi? Ama denizdeyiz.
Come on, guys, focus!
Hadi millet, odaklanın!
Hoist the sails and start paddling!
Yelkenleri toplayıp küreklere asılın!
Put the ship back on course, now!
Eski rotamıza dönelim!
As you wish, Nami!
Emredersin, Nami-san!
What are you panicking about?
Niye evhamlanıyorsun ki?
And why paddle? This is a sailboat.
Kürek çekmek mi? Bu bir yelkenli.
Yeah, why?
Adam haklı.
Why bother when the Marines are back there?
Denizcilerden yeni kaçtık, niye geri dönelim ki?
Just shut up and do as I say! We're in big trouble!
Hemen dediğimi yapın! Başımız büyük dertte!
But the sea is nice and quiet here.
Ama deniz sakin görünüyor.
Yeah.
Öyle.
Alright, fine! I'll explain!
Off, tamam! Anlatayım size!
Listen. Since we were in such a hurry, we went farther south than intended!
Dinleyin. Aceleyle kaçarken, planladığımızdan daha güneye geldik!
So we're in the Grand Line now?
O halde Grand Line'a mı girdik?
Alright!
Yaşasın!
If it was that easy, anyone could enter!
O kadar kolay olsaydı, Grand Line'a herkes girerdi!
Look here.
Bakın.
The Grand Line runs between these two strips of sea.
Grand Line, iki başka deniz arasında sıkışmıştır!
Are you following? The two strips are called the Calm Belts.
Anladınız mı? Bu denizlere Calm Belt denir.
The reason's unknown, but no wind or currents flow through them.
Sebebi bilinmez, bu bölgelerde ne rüzgâr eser, ne de akıntı vardır.
These seas are completely calm.
Bu denizler tamamen durgundur.
Sailboats need wind to move so it's very dangerous—
Yelkenliler için, bu bölgelerde yolculuk yapmak...
maybe even fatal—without it!
çok tehlikelidir!
Did you get all that, Luffy?
Luffy, anladın mı?
Yeah. Basically, we're in trouble.
Evet. Kısaca, başımız belada.
I see. Good, you got more than I thought.
Aynen öyle. Anlamana sevindim.
So that's why the geezer said it was dangerous...
Yani o moruk tehlikeli dediğinde, kastettiği bu muydu?
That explains the lack of wind.
Bu, rüzgârın olmayışını açıklıyor.
Not much we can do if the ship can't move.
Gemi kıpırdamazsa hiçbir şey yapamayız.
Can't we just wait for wind to–
Sadece rüzgârı beklesek–
I just explained this! Wind won't blow no matter how long you wait here!
Bunu az önce açıkladım! İstediğin kadar bekle, rüzgâr esmez!
And that's not all!
Ve dahası da var!
There's another reason this area is dangerous!
Bu bölgenin tehlikeli olmasının başka bir sebebi daha var!
The Calm Belt is–
Bu yer–
What's going on?
Ne oluyor?
They're huge!
Kocamanlar!
The Calm Belt is a nest of sea kings.
Calm Belt, deniz krallarının yuvasıdır.
Specifically colossal ones.
Özellikle devasa olanların.
They're the other reason people can't cross the Calm Belt...
İnsanların Calm Belt'ten geçememelerinin bir başka sebebi de onlar.
What do we do now?
Şimdi ne yapacağız?
They'll go back into the sea eventually.
Önünde sonunda denize geri döneceklerdir.
When they do, we paddle as hard as possible.
Sonra tüm gücümüzle kürek çekeceğiz.
Are you serious?!
Ciddi misin sen?!
Shut it, idiot!
Seni salak!
Sorry...
Özür...
Hold on a sec...!
Bekle bir saniye...!
If it does that...
Yoksa o...
He's gonna sneeze!
Hapşıracak!
– What?!
– Ne?!
Wow! It feels like we're flying!
Süper! Sanki uçuyoruz!
We are flying!
Gerçekten uçuyoruz!!
Looks like we're back on course...
Görünüşe göre asıl rotamıza döndük...
We should be seeing the Red Line any moment now.
Red Line'ı her an görebiliriz...
Are we finally going into the Grand Line?!
Sonunda Grand Line'a ulaşıyoruz!
Hey, Sanji! We're here, we're here, we're finally here!
Hey, Sanji! Oraya varıyoruz. Sonunda varıyoruz!
That hurts!
Acıtıyor!
Sorry...
Afedersin...
Zoro!
Zoro!
But... We're here, we're here!
Ama... Oraya varıyoruz!
We're here, we're here, we're here! is the drawing an accurate representation of what we'll find?
Bu harita doğru çizilmiş mi? Sonunda varıyoruz!
Quit it!
Kes şunu!!!
Look at this!
Şuna bakın!
I'd heard the rumors about it, and it's drawn on this map, too!
Bazı şeyler duymuştum, üstelik, bu haritaya da çizilmiş!
If all of that is true, then the entrance to the Grand Line is a mountain!
Eğer gerçekten doğruysa, Grand Line'ın girişi bir dağ!
A mountain?
Dağ mı?
We gotta crash into it?
Dağa mı çarpacağız?
You're kidding, right?
Cidden mi?
I doubted it myself, but the map shows canals leading to the mountain.
Ben de inanmamıştım ama haritada dağa çıkan kanallar var.
That might mean we have to go up it!
Yani yukarı çıkmamız gerekebilir!
Cool!
Çok iyi be!
What are you talking about?!
Ne diyorsun sen?!
Even with canals or whatever, a ship can't climb up a mountain!
Kanal olsun olmasın, bir gemi dağa çıkamaz!
But that's what the map says!
Ama harita öyle söylüyor!
Exactly! Nami would never say anything wrong!
Evet! Nami-san asla yanılmaz!
You stole that map from Buggy, right?
Bu haritayı Buggy'den çalmıştın, değil mi?
Can we really trust it?
Güvenilir mi ki?
H-Hey!
H-Hey!
Someone help me move the whipstaff!
Biri dümene yardım etsin!
Sanji! Give Usopp a hand!
Sanji-kun! Usopp'a yardım et!
It won't budge!
Kımıldamıyor bile!
I can't think with all his shouting!
Bu bağırış çağırışta düşünemiyorum!
It won't move! Someone help!
Kımıldamıyor! Biri yardım etsin!
Right away, Nami!
Hemen, Nami-san!
Here I go!
Tamam!
D-Doesn't this current seem a bit strong?!
B-Bu akıntı çok güçlü değil mi?!
Huh?
Ne?!
Usopp, say that again!
Usopp! Ne dedin sen?
"D-Doesn't this current seem a bit strong?!"
"B-Bu akıntı çok güçlü değil mi?!"
Current...
Akıntı...
That's it!
İşte bu!
What's it?
Ne oldu?
The canals do go up the mountain!
Gerçekten dağa doğru gidiyorlar!
You're still on that?
Hâlâ mı aynı muhabbet?!
Look here!
Bakın!
See?
Gördünüz mü?
The guiding light was definitely pointing to here.
Işık buraya işaret ediyor olmalı...
Right on the Red Line: Reverse Mountain!
Red Line'daki Reverse Mountain!
Hey! What do I do now?!
Hey! Bi el atsanıza buraya!
See these canals here?
Bu kanalları görüyor musunuz?
If major currents from the four seas all flowed toward this mountain...
Eğer dört denizin güçlü akıntıları bu dağa doğru akıyorsa...
Then the four currents would go up these canals, collide at the top,
dört akıntı da bu kanallardan yukarıya doğru çıkıp zirvede birleşir...
and flow into the Grand Line!
ve Grand Line'a dökülür!
Reverse Mountain is a winter island,
Reverse Mountain bir kış adası,...
so any currents that collide with the Red Line will go into the depths.
yani Red Line'a çarpan tüm akıntılar yüzeyden dimdik derine doğru iner.
If we screw up and miss the entrance to the canal...
Eğer kanalın girişini kaçırıp işi bok edersek...
the Going Merry will crash into the Red Line...
Going Merry, Red Line'a bodoslama çarpar...
and get completely wrecked!
ve paramparça olur!
Then we'd end up at the bottom of the ocean. Get it?
Ve biz de denizin dibini boylarız. Anladınız mı?
Oh, very interesting!
Ah! Baya ilginçmiş!
So, basically, it's a mystery mountain!
Yani basitçe, gizemli bir dağ!
Well, I guess you wouldn't...
Hiç anlamamışsın...
All in all, now that we're on this current,
Neyse, bu gemi şu anda o akıntıların birinde.
as long as we steer correctly,
Eğer kontrolümüzü yitirmezsek,...
it's a straight shot to the summit of Reverse Mountain!
Reverse Mountain'a tek parça olarak çıkarız.
You're amazing, Nami!
Nami-san! Harikasın!
I've never heard of someone going up a mountain by boat.
Daha önce hiç dağa çıkan bi' gemi duymamıştım.
I've heard some stories!
Ben bir şeyler duymuştum!
About the mystery mountain?
Bu dağ hakkında mı?
No.
Hayır.
I heard that half of everyone who heads to the Grand Line die before entering...
Grand Line'a gidenlerin yarısı daha giremeden ölüyormuş...
I knew getting in wouldn't be easy.
Girmenin kolay olmayacağını biliyordum.
Sanji! Could you get the sail?
Sanji-kun! Yelkenlere sende!
Of course, Nami!
Emredersin, Nami-san!
Luffy! Help out!
Luffy! Bir el at!
What?!
Ne?!
Hey!
Hey!
I see the mystery mountain!
Gizemli dağ göründü!
– Wh-What?! – What?!
– N-Ne?! – Ne dedin?!
Th-That's insanely huge!
K-Kocaman!!
So that's the Red Line, huh?!
Demek bu Red Line, ha?!
Th-Th-The t-top's all the way above the clouds!
T-T-Tepesi bulutların ötesinde!
We're getting sucked in!
Bizi içine çekiyor!
Hold the rudder tight!
Dümeni sağlam tutun!
– On it!
– Hallediyoruz!
N-Nami! Wh-Where's the entrance?!
N-Nami! G-Giriş nerede?!
We're gonna crash if we keep going this way!
Bu şekilde devam edersek çarpacağız!
The crack in that cliff...
Kayalıktaki yarık...
Nami! What do we do?!
Nami! Ne yapalım?!
Keep going straight ahead!
Dümdüz devam edin!
Are you sure?!
Emin misin?!
Just do it!
Evet!
Nami! Is that the entrance?
Nami! Şu kanal girişi mi?
Most likely!
Büyük ihtimal!
I can't believe this...!
Gözlerime inanamıyorum!
The damn ocean really is flowing up the mountain!
Kahrolası deniz cidden dağa doğru akıyor!
We gotta be careful sailing through those gates!
Bu geçitlerden sorunsuzca geçmemiz gerekiyor!
If we don't get it just right, the ship is done for!
Aksi takdirde gemi paramparça olur!
W-We're a little off! More to the right! The right!
R-Rotadan sapıyoruz! Sağa doğru! Sağa! Sağa!
The right?! Go starboard!
Sağa mı?! Sancak alabanda!
C-Come on, now!
H-Hadi, yüklen!
– The whipstaff!
– Dümen kolu!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
Lastik-Lastik Balon!
Luffy!
Luffy!
Grab on!
Bana tutun!
– We made it!
– Başardık!
Now it's just a straight shot to the summit!
Şimdi alabildiğine zirveye doğru!
A-Awesome!
M-Müthiş!
Awesome, right?
Harika, değil mi?
We're in the clouds!
Bulutların içindeyiz!
So cool!
Müthiş!!!
Now we're above the clouds!
Bulutların üstüne çıktık!
Look! It's the summit! The summit!
Bakın! Zirve! Zirve orada!
Yahoo!
Yaşasın!
I see it!
Görüyorum!
This is the greatest sea in the world!
İşte dünyanın en büyük denizi!
The Grand Line!
Grand Line!
The One Piece is somewhere up ahead!
One Piece orada bir yerde!
Go!
Gidelim!
Did you hear that just now?
Siz de duydunuz mu?
Wasn't it just the wind?
Rüzgârı mı diyorsun?
It must be from all the weird landforms around here.
Herhâlde çevredeki tuhaf oluşumlardan kaynaklı.
What's that?
O ne?
Nami! I see a mountain up ahead!
Nami-san! İleride bir dağ görüyorum!
A mountain?! That can't be right!
Dağ mı?! Bu imkânsız!
But there's really one there!
Ama görüyorum!
Who cares?! Go!
Kimin umrunda?! Gidelim!!
It should be open sea once we pass the Twin Capes up ahead!
İkiz Burun'u geçer geçmez açık denize ulaşmalıyız!
Oh, crap!
Hassiktir!!
It's not a mountain!
Dağ değilmiş!
It's a big black wall!
Siyah bir duvar bu!
No, it's not! That's...
Hayır, değil! Bu...
What is it then?!
O zaman ne?!
I-I-I-It's...
B-B-Bu...
It's a whale!
Balina!
Wh-Wh-What are we g-gonna do?!
N-N-Ne halt e-edeceğiz şimdi?!
We should fight it!
Dövelim mi?
Are you crazy?! How are we gonna fight that?!
Aptal! Bu şeyi nasıl döveceğiz?!
B-B-But, i-i-it's blocking our way!
A-A-A-Ama yolumuzu kapatıyor!
What are we gonna do?!
Ne yapacağız?!
Hold on a sec!
Durun bir saniye!
If it looks like a wall from this close, where are its eyes?!
Yakından bir duvara benziyorsa o zaman gözleri nerede?!
That's right! Maybe it hasn't noticed us yet!
Doğru! Bizi görmemiş olabilir!
Either way, we're about to crash into it!
Ama bir şey yapmazsak çarpacağız!
Hey! There's an opening on the left!
Hey! Sol tarafından geçebiliriz!
Port! Hard to port!
İskele! İskele alabanda!
But the whipstaff is broken!
Ama dümen kolu kırık!
Well, figure something out! I'll help!
Bir şey yapın! Ben de yardım edeceğim!
Oh, yeah!
Ah, evet!
I've got an idea!
Bir fikrim var!
Luffy...?
Luffy...?
Hey, what are you doing?!
Hey, napıyorsun?!
This isn't working!
Olmuyor!
The ship won't turn!
Gemi dönmüyor!
Dammit!
Kahretsin!
Don't give up!
Pes etmeyin!
Is this it...?!
Her şey bitti mi...?!
The cannon?!
Top mu?!
Alright! Did it stop?
Pekâlâ! Durdu mu ki?
We're screwed...
Ayvayı yedik...
Yeah, this is it...
Bittik...
My special seat!
Özel koltuğum!
Let's...
Çok...
Let's book it while we still can!
Çok geç olmadan tüyelim!
What the heck is going on?!
Ne oluyor, lan?!
Is it so big that it didn't even feel it?!
Çok büyük diye mi hissetmedi?!
Or is it just slow?!
Yoksa çok mu yavaş?!
Who cares?! Let's get the hell out of here!
Kim bilir?! Neyse, hadi sıvışalım!
My ears!
Kulaklarım!
Paddle! Just keep paddling!
Kürek çekin! Asılın küreklere!
We have to get away from it!
Ondan uzaklaşmamız lazım!
Luffy...?
Luffy...?
You!
Sen!
What the hell did you do to my special seat?!
Özel koltuğuma ne yaptın lan?!
– You dumbass!
– Seni salak!
How was that, huh?! Bring it on, you bastard!
Nasılmış?! Yiyosa gel, şerefsiz!
– Shut up already, you idiot!
– Kes artık, aptal!
Wh-What?
N-Ne?
Luffy!
Luffy!
I'm not gonna die!
Ölmeyeceğim!
What am I gonna do?
Şimdi ne yapacağım?
They all got eaten...
Herkesi yedi...
Hey, you! Spit them out! Give everyone back!
Hey, sen! Geri tükür! Onları geri ver!
Spit them out already! Listen to me!
Tükür onları artık! Beni dinle!
You–
Ulan–
You... You jerk!
Seni... pislik!
Are you diving?! Stop it!
Dalıyor musun?! Dursana!
Hey! I said stop! Hey!
Hey! Dur dedim! Hey!
Please, stop! Give my friends back!
Lütfen, dur! Arkadaşlarımı geri ver!
Hey!
Hey!
Stop it already!
Dur artık!
We were just about to go on an adventure!
Onlarla maceralara atılacaktık!
I can't lose them!
Onları kaybedemem!
Give them back!
Geri ver onları!
So, what do you think?
Ne düşünüyorsun...?
What do I think...?
Ne mi düşünüyorum...?
What should I think?
Ne düşünmeliyim?
H-H-H-H-How...?
N-N-N-N-Ne...?
We were definitely swallowed by that whale...
Balina tarafından yutulduğumuza emindim...
Is this a dream?
Rüya mı bu?
Yeah, it's gotta be a dream.
Evet, muhtemelen.
Then, how do you explain that island and house?
Peki, bu ada ve ev, burada ne arıyor?
Hallucinations.
Halüsinasyon.
So, that's also...?
O zaman, bu...?
– It's an imperial squid!
– Dev bir kalamar!
Looks like someone lives there.
Görünüşe göre burada biri var.
Let's hope they're human.
Umarım bi' insandır...
I've had enough. I wanna go home.
Yetti artık bana. Eve gitmek istiyorum.
Luffy's gone, too... What's gonna happen to us?
Luffy de gitti. Bize ne olacak?
You're right! Where's Luffy?!
Doğru ya, Luffy nerede?!
What the heck is all this?
Bu ne lan?
Why is there a door to a hallway inside a whale?
Niye balinanın içinde kapı ve koridor var?
A ship...
Bir gemi...
Sh-Sh-Should we f-fire the cannon at that island?!
T-T-Topu ateşlesek mi adaya doğru?!
No, hold on a sec...
Hayır, durun bir saniye...
Someone's coming out...
Biri dışarı çıkıyor...